Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
- Videorecordings
  - Videorecordings, 2001
    - No. 0118, 2001-05-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0433 (Box 43)
    - No. 0119, 2001-05-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0434 (Box 43)
    - No. 0120, 2001-05-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0434 (Box 43)
    - No. 0121, 2001-05-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0434 (Box 43)
    - No. 0122, 2001-06-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0435 (Box 43)
    - No. 0123, 2001-06-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0435 (Box 43)
    - No. 0124, 2001-06-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0435 (Box 43)
    - No. 0125, 2001-06-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0436 (Box 43)
    - No. 0126, 2001-06-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0436 (Box 43)
    - No. 0127, 2001-07-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0436 (Box 43)
    - No. 0128, 2001-07-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0437 (Box 43)
    - No. 0129, 2001-07-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0437 (Box 43)
    - No. 0130, 2001-07-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0437 (Box 43)
    - No. 0131, 2001-08-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0438 (Box 44)
    - No. 0132, 2001-08-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0438 (Box 44)
    - No. 0133, 2001-08-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0438 (Box 44)
    - No. 0134, 2001-08-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0439 (Box 44)
    - No. 0135, 2001-08-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0439 (Box 44)
    - No. 0136, 2001-09-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0439 (Box 44)
    - No. 0137, 2001-09-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0440 (Box 44)
    - No. 0138, 2001-09-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0440 (Box 44)
    - No. 0139, 2001-09-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0440 (Box 44)
    - No. 0140, 2001-10-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0441 (Box 44)
    - No. 0141, 2001-10-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0441 (Box 44)
    - No. 0142, 2001-10-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0441 (Box 44)
    - No. 0143, 2001-10-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0442 (Box 44)
    - No. 0144, 2001-11-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0442 (Box 44)
    - No. 0145, 2001-11-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0442 (Box 44)
    - No. 0146, 2001-11-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0443 (Box 44)
    - No. 0147, 2001-11-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0443 (Box 44)
    - No. 0148, 2001-11-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0443 (Box 44)
    - No. 0149, 2001-12-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0444 (Box 44)
    - No. 0150, 2001-12-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0444 (Box 44)
    - No. 0151, 2001-12-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0444 (Box 44)
    - No. 0152, 2001-12-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0445 (Box 44)
  - Videorecordings, 2002
    - No. 0201, 2002-01-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0445 (Box 44)
    - No. 0202, 2002-01-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0445 (Box 44)
    - No. 0203, 2002-01-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0446 (Box 44)
    - No. 0204, 2002-01-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0446 (Box 44)
    - No. 0205, 2002-02-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0446 (Box 44)
    - No. 0206, 2002-02-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0447 (Box 44)
    - No. 0207, 2002-02-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0447 (Box 44)
    - No. 0208, 2002-02-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0447 (Box 44)
    - No. 0209, 2002-03-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0448 (Box 44)
    - No. 0210, 2002-03-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0448 (Box 44)
    - No. 0211, 2002-03-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0448 (Box 44)
    - No. 0212, 2002-03-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0449 (Box 44)
    - No. 0213, 2002-03-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0449 (Box 44)
    - No. 0214, 2002-04-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0449 (Box 44)
    - No. 0215, 2002-04-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0450 (Box 44)
    - No. 0216, 2002-04-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0450 (Box 44)
    - No. 0217, 2002-04-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0450 (Box 44)
    - No. 0218, 2002-05-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0451 (Box 45)
    - No. 0219, 2002-05-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0451 (Box 45)
    - No. 0220, 2002-05-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0451 (Box 45)
    - No. 0221, 2002-05-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0452 (Box 45)
    - No. 0222, 2002-05-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0452 (Box 45)
    - No. 0223, 2002-06-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0452 (Box 45)
    - No. 0224, 2002-06-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0453 (Box 45)
    - No. 0225, 2002-06-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0453 (Box 45)
    - No. 0226, 2002-06-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0453 (Box 45)
    - No. 0227, 2002-07-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0454 (Box 45)
    - No. 0228, 2002-07-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0454 (Box 45)
    - No. 0229, 2002-07-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0454 (Box 45)
    - No. 0230, 2002-07-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0455 (Box 45)
    - No. 0231, 2002-08-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0455 (Box 45)
    - No. 0232, 2002-08-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0455 (Box 45)
    - No. 0233, 2002-08-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0456 (Box 45)
    - No. 0234, 2002-08-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0456 (Box 45)
    - No. 0235, 2002-08-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0456 (Box 45)
    - No. 0236, 2002-09-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0457 (Box 45)
    - No. 0237, 2002-09-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0457 (Box 45)
    - No. 0238, 2002-09-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0457 (Box 45)
    - No. 0239, 2002-09-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0458 (Box 45)
    - No. 0240, 2002-10-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0458 (Box 45)
    - No. 0241, 2002-10-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0458 (Box 45)
    - No. 0242, 2002-10-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0459 (Box 45)
    - No. 0243, 2002-10-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0459 (Box 45)
    - No. 0244, 2002-11-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0459 (Box 45)
    - No. 0245, 2002-11-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0460 (Box 45)
    - No. 0246, 2002-11-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0460 (Box 45)
    - No. 0247, 2002-11-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0460 (Box 45)
    - No. 0248, 2002-11-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0461 (Box 45)
    - No. 0249, 2002-12-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0461 (Box 45)
    - No. 0250, 2002-12-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0461 (Box 45)
    - No. 0251, 2002-12-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0462 (Box 45)
    - No. 0252, 2002-12-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0462 (Box 45)
  - Videorecordings, 2003
    - No. 0301, 2003-01-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0462 (Box 45)
    - No. 0302, 2003-01-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0463 (Box 45)
    - No. 0303, 2003-01-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0463 (Box 45)
    - No. 0304, 2003-01-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0463 (Box 45)
    - No. 0305, 2003-01-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0464 (Box 46)
    - No. 0306, 2003-02-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0464 (Box 46)
    - No. 0307, 2003-02-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0464 (Box 46)
    - No. 0308, 2003-02-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0465 (Box 46)
    - No. 0309, 2003-02-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0465 (Box 46)
    - No. 0310, 2003-03-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0465 (Box 46)
    - No. 0311, 2003-03-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0466 (Box 46)
    - No. 0312, 2003-03-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0466 (Box 46)
    - No. 0313, 2003-03-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0466 (Box 46)
    - No. 0314, 2003-04-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0467 (Box 46)
    - No. 0315, 2003-04-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0467 (Box 46)
    - No. 0316, 2003-04-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0467 (Box 46)
    - No. 0317, 2003-04-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0468 (Box 46)
    - No. 0318, 2003-05-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0468 (Box 46)
    - No. 0319, 2003-05-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0468 (Box 46)
    - No. 0320, 2003-05-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0469 (Box 46)
    - No. 0321, 2003-05-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0469 (Box 46)
    - No. 0322, 2003-05-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0469 (Box 46)
    - No. 0323, 2003-06-06; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0470 (Box 46)
    - No. 0324, 2003-06-13; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0470 (Box 46)
    - No. 0325, 2003-06-20; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0470 (Box 46)
    - No. 0326, 2003-06-27; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0470 (Box 46)
    - No. 0327, 2003-07-04; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0470 (Box 46)
    - No. 0328, 2003-07-11; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0470 (Box 46)
    - No. 0329, 2003-07-18; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0471 (Box 46)
    - No. 0330, 2003-07-25; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0471 (Box 46)
    - No. 0331, 2003-08-01; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0471 (Box 46)
    - No. 0332, 2003-08-08; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0471 (Box 46)
    - No. 0333, 2003-08-15; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0471 (Box 46)
    - No. 0334, 2003-08-22; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0471 (Box 46)
    - No. 0335, 2003-08-29; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0472 (Box 46)
    - No. 0336, 2003-09-05; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0472 (Box 46)
    - No. 0337, 2003-09-12; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0472 (Box 46)
    - No. 0338, 2003-09-19; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0472 (Box 46)
    - No. 0339, 2003-09-26; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0472 (Box 46)
    - No. 0340, 2003-10-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0472 (Box 46)
    - No. 0341, 2003-10-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0473 (Box 46)
    - No. 0342, 2003-10-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0473 (Box 46)
    - No. 0343, 2003-10-24; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0473 (Box 46)
    - No. 0344, 2003-10-31; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0473 (Box 46)
    - No. 0345, 2003-11-07; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0473 (Box 46)
    - No. 0346, 2003-11-14; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0473 (Box 46)
    - No. 0347, 2003-11-21; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0474 (Box 46)
    - No. 0348, 2003-11-28; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0474 (Box 46)
    - No. 0349, 2003-12-05; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0474 (Box 46)
    - No. 0350, 2003-12-12; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0474 (Box 46)
    - No. 0351, 2003-12-19; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0474 (Box 46)
    - No. 0352, 2003-12-26; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0474 (Box 46)
  - Videorecordings, 2004
    - No. 0401, 2004-01-02; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0475 (Box 46)
    - No. 0402, 2004-01-09; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0475 (Box 46)
    - No. 0403, 2004-01-16; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0475 (Box 46)
    - No. 0404, 2004-01-23; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0475 (Box 46)
    - No. 0405, 2004-01-30; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0475 (Box 46)
    - No. 0406, 2004-02-06; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0475 (Box 46)
    - No. 0407, 2004-02-13; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0476 (Box 46)
    - No. 0408, 2004-02-20; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0476 (Box 46)
    - No. 0409, 2004-02-27; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0476 (Box 46)
    - No. 0410, 2004-03-05; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0476 (Box 46)
    - No. 0411, 2004-03-12; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0476 (Box 46)
    - No. 0412, 2004-03-19; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0476 (Box 46)
    - No. 0413, 2004-03-26; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0477 (Box 46)
    - No. 0414, 2004-04-02; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0477 (Box 46)
    - No. 0415, 2004-04-09; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0477 (Box 46)
    - No. 0416, 2004-04-16; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0477 (Box 46)
    - No. 0417, 2004-04-23; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0477 (Box 46)
    - No. 0418, 2004-04-30; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0477 (Box 46)
    - No. 0419, 2004-05-07; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0478 (Box 46)
    - No. 0420, 2004-05-14; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0478 (Box 46)
    - No. 0421, 2004-05-21; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0478 (Box 46)
    - No. 0422, 2004-05-28; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0478 (Box 46)
    - No. 0423, 2004-06-04; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0478 (Box 46)
    - No. 0424, 2004-06-11; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0478 (Box 46)
    - No. 0425, 2004-06-18; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0479 (Box 46)
    - No. 0426, 2004-06-25; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0479 (Box 46)
    - No. 0427, 2004-07-02; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0479 (Box 46)
    - No. 0428, 2004-07-09; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0479 (Box 46)
    - No. 0429, 2004-07-16; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0479 (Box 46)
    - No. 0430, 2004-07-23; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0479 (Box 46)
    - No. 0431, 2004-07-30; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0480 (Box 46)
    - No. 0432, 2004-08-06; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0480 (Box 46)
    - No. 0433, 2004-08-13; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0480 (Box 46)
    - No. 0434, 2004-08-20; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0480 (Box 46)
    - No. 0435, 2004-08-27; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0480 (Box 46)
    - No. 0436, 2004-09-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0480 (Box 46)
    - No. 0437, 2004-09-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0481 (Box 46)
    - No. 0438, 2004-09-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0481 (Box 46)
    - No. 0439, 2004-09-24; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0481 (Box 46)
    - No. 0440, 2004-10-01; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0481 (Box 46)
    - No. 0441, 2004-10-08; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0481 (Box 46)
    - No. 0442, 2004-10-15; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0481 (Box 46)
    - No. 0443, 2004-10-22; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0482 (Box 46)
    - No. 0444, 2004-10-29; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0482 (Box 46)
    - No. 0445, 2004-11-05; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0482 (Box 46)
    - No. 0446, 2004-11-12; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0482 (Box 46)
    - No. 0447, 2004-11-19; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0482 (Box 46)
    - No. 0448, 2004-11-26; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0482 (Box 46)
    - No. 0449, 2004-12-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0483 (Box 46)
    - No. 0450, 2004-12-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0483 (Box 46)
    - No. 0451, 2004-12-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0483 (Box 46)
    - No. 0452, 2004-12-24; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0483 (Box 46)
    - No. 0501, 2004-12-31; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0483 (Box 46)
  - Videorecordings, 2005
    - No. 0502, 2005-01-07; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0483 (Box 46)
    - No. 0503, 2005-01-14; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0484 (Box 46)
    - No. 0504, 2005-01-21; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0484 (Box 46)
    - No. 0505, 2005-01-28; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0484 (Box 46)
    - No. 0506, 2005-02-04; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0484 (Box 46)
    - No. 0507, 2005-02-11; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0484 (Box 46)
    - No. 0508, 2005-02-18; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0484 (Box 46)
    - No. 0509, 2005-02-25; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0485 (Box 46)
    - No. 0510, 2005-03-04; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0485 (Box 46)
    - No. 0511, 2005-03-11; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0485 (Box 46)
    - No. 0512, 2005-03-18; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0485 (Box 46)
    - No. 0513, 2005-03-25; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0485 (Box 46)
    - No. 0514, 2005-04-01; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0485 (Box 46)
    - No. 0515, 2005-04-08; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0486 (Box 46)
    - No. 0516, 2005-04-15; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0486 (Box 46)
    - No. 0517, 2005-04-22; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0486 (Box 46)
    - No. 0518, 2005-04-29; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0486 (Box 46)
    - No. 0519, 2005-05-06; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0486 (Box 46)
    - No. 0520, 2005-05-13; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0486 (Box 46)
    - No. 0521, 2005-05-20; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0487 (Box 46)
    - No. 0522, 2005-05-27; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0487 (Box 46)
    - No. 0523, 2005-06-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0487 (Box 46)
    - No. 0524, 2005-06-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0487 (Box 46)
    - No. 0525, 2005-06-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0487 (Box 46)
    - No. 0526, 2005-06-24; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0487 (Box 46)
    - No. 0527, 2005-07-01; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0488 (Box 46)
    - No. 0528, 2005-07-08; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0488 (Box 46)
    - No. 0529, 2005-07-15; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0488 (Box 46)
    - No. 0530, 2005-07-22; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0488 (Box 46)
    - No. 0531, 2005-07-29; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0488 (Box 46)
    - No. 0532, 2005-08-05; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0488 (Box 46)
    - No. 0533, 2005-08-12; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0489 (Box 46)
    - No. 0534, 2005-08-19; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0489 (Box 46)
    - No. 0535, 2005-08-26; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0489 (Box 46)
    - No. 0536, 2005-09-02; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0489 (Box 46)
    - No. 0537, 2005-09-09; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0489 (Box 46)
    - No. 0538, 2005-09-16; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0489 (Box 46)
    - No. 0539, 2005-09-23; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0490 (Box 46)
    - No. 0540, 2005-09-30; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0490 (Box 46)
    - No. 0541, 2005-10-07; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0490 (Box 46)
    - No. 0542, 2005-10-14; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0490 (Box 46)
    - No. 0543, 2005-10-21; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0490 (Box 46)
    - No. 0544, 2005-10-28; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0490 (Box 46)
    - No. 0545, 2005-11-04; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0491 (Box 46)
    - No. 0546, 2005-11-11; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0491 (Box 46)
    - No. 0547, 2005-11-18; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0491 (Box 46)
    - No. 0548, 2005-11-25; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0491 (Box 46)
    - No. 0549, 2005-12-02; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0491 (Box 46)
    - No. 0550, 2005-12-09; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0491 (Box 46)
    - No. 0551, 2005-12-16; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0492 (Box 46)
    - No. 0552, 2005-12-23; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0492 (Box 46)
    - No. 0553, 2005-12-30; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0492 (Box 46)
  - Videorecordings, 2006
    - No. 0601, 2006-01-06; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0492 (Box 46)
    - No. 0602, 2006-01-13; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0492 (Box 46)
    - No. 0603, 2006-01-20; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0492 (Box 46)
    - No. 0604, 2006-01-27; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0493 (Box 46)
    - No. 0605, 2006-02-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0493 (Box 46)
    - No. 0606, 2006-02-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0493 (Box 46)
    - No. 0607, 2006-02-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0493 (Box 46)
    - No. 0608, 2006-02-24; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0493 (Box 46)
    - No. 0609, 2006-03-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0493 (Box 46)
    - No. 0610, 2006-03-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0494 (Box 46)
    - No. 0611, 2006-03-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0494 (Box 46)
    - No. 0612, 2006-03-24; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0494 (Box 46)
    - No. 0613, 2006-03-31; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0494 (Box 46)
    - No. 0614, 2006-04-07; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0494 (Box 46)
    - No. 0615, 2006-04-14; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0494 (Box 46)
    - No. 0616, 2006-04-21; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0495 (Box 46)
    - No. 0617, 2006-04-28; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0495 (Box 46)
    - No. 0618, 2006-05-05; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0495 (Box 46)
    - No. 0619, 2006-05-12; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0495 (Box 46)
    - No. 0620, 2006-05-19; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0495 (Box 46)
    - No. 0621, 2006-05-26; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0495 (Box 46)
    - No. 0622, 2006-06-02; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0496 (Box 46)
    - No. 0623, 2006-06-09; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0496 (Box 46)
    - No. 0624, 2006-06-16; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0496 (Box 46)
    - No. 0625, 2006-06-23; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0496 (Box 46)
    - No. 0626, 2006-06-30; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0496 (Box 46)
    - No. 0627, 2006-07-07; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0496 (Box 46)
    - No. 0628, 2006-07-14; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0497 (Box 46)
    - No. 0629, 2006-07-21; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0497 (Box 46)
    - No. 0630, 2006-07-28; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0497 (Box 46)
    - No. 0631, 2006-08-04; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0497 (Box 46)
    - No. 0632, 2006-08-11; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0497 (Box 46)
    - No. 0633, 2006-08-18; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0497 (Box 46)
    - No. 0634, 2006-08-25; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0498 (Box 46)
    - No. 0635, 2006-09-01; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0498 (Box 46)
    - No. 0636, 2006-09-08; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0498 (Box 46)
    - No. 0637, 2006-09-15; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0498 (Box 46)
    - No. 0638, 2006-09-22; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0498 (Box 46)
    - No. 0639, 2006-09-29; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0498 (Box 46)
    - No. 0640, 2006-10-06; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0499 (Box 46)
    - No. 0641, 2006-10-13; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0499 (Box 46)
    - No. 0642, 2006-10-20; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0499 (Box 46)
    - No. 0643, 2006-10-27; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0499 (Box 46)
    - No. 0644, 2006-11-03; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0499 (Box 46)
    - No. 0645, 2006-11-10; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0499 (Box 46)
    - No. 0646, 2006-11-17; DVCAM; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0500 (Box 46)